wwt.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy - WWT

This policy describes how World Wide Technology (including its subsidiaries and affiliates) collects, uses, and shares personal information on its website and mobile devices.

## Types of Data We Collect

Personal information means information that allows someone to identify or contact you. Non-personal information means information that does not directly identify you. We collect both types of information about you.

The following provides some examples of the type of data that we collect from you:

Context | Types of Data and Purpose for Collection  
---|---  
Account Registration | We may collect your name and contact information when you create an account.  
Demographic Information | We may collect personal information from you, such as your age, photo, or location.   
Email Interconnectivity | If you receive email from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links or banners it contains and make purchases.  
Employment | If you apply for a job posting, or become an employee, we may collect personal information necessary to process your application. This may include, among other things, your tax identification number.  
Feedback/Support | If you provide us feedback or contact us for support we will collect your name and e-mail address and possibly other personal information, as well as any other content that you send to us in order to reply.  
Mailing List | When you sign up for one of our mailing lists we may collect your email address or postal address.  
Mobile Devices | We may collect information from your mobile device such as unique identifying information broadcast from your device or hardware and software specifications. We may also ask you if you would like to share your location information from your mobile device.  
Order Placement | We may collect your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number when you place an order.  
Partner Promotion | We may collect information that you provide as part of a co-branded promotion with another company.  
Surveys | When you participate in a survey we may collect additional information that you provide through the survey. If the survey is provided by a third-party service provider, the third party’s privacy policy applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information.  
Third Party Tracking | We participate in behavior-based advertising. This means that a third party may use technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about your use of our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests. That advertising may appear either on our websites, or on other websites. You can opt-out of receiving advertising based upon your browsing behavior from some network advertising companies by going to the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance websites.  
Web logs | We may collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet), domain name, click-activity, referring website, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. In addition to information stored by our servers, we may also use cookies and clear GIFs. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your device until you delete them). Among other things, cookies allow us to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience. Persistent cookies may be removed by following instructions provided by your browser. If you choose to disable cookies some areas or features of our websites may not work properly.  
  
In addition to the information that we collect from you directly, we may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, business partners, our affiliates, or publicly available sources.

## How We Use and Process Your Personal Data

In addition to the uses described above, we use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To identify you when you visit our websites or use one of our mobile apps
  * To perform under a contract
  * To provide the products and services you request
  * To improve our services and product offerings
  * To conduct analytics
  * To respond to your inquiries related to support, employment opportunities, or other requests
  * For internal administrative purposes, as well as to manage our relationship with you

## How We Share Your Personal Data

In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this policy, we disclose personal information in the following situations:

  * **Afilliates and Acquisitions** We may share your personal information with our corporate affiliates (e.g., parent company, sister companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control). If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, we will also share your personal information with that company.
  * **Other Disclosures with Your Consent** We may ask if you would like us to share your information with other unaffiliated third parties who are not described elsewhere in this policy.
  * **Other Disclosures without Your Consent** We may disclose personal information in response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, or to comply with relevant laws. We may also share your personal information in order to establish or exercise our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies.
  * **Service Providers** We may share your personal information with service providers. Among other things service providers may help us to administer our website, conduct surveys, and provide technical support.
  * **Suppliers** We may share your personal information with our suppliers

## Your Choices

You can make the following choices regarding your Personal Data:

  * **Changes To Your Personal Information** We rely on you to update and correct your personal information. Note that we may keep historical information in our backup files as permitted by law. All requests to correct your information must be directed to the contact in the “How You May Contact Us Regarding Your Personal Information” section below.
  * **Deletion Of Your Personal Data** Typically, we retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Some users may have the right to request that we delete their personal information. All deletion requests must be directed to the contact in the “How You May Contact Us Regarding Your Personal Information” section below. We may also decide to delete your data if we believe that the data is incomplete, inaccurate, or that our continued use and storage are contrary to our obligations to other individuals or third parties. When we delete personal information, it will be removed from our active database, but it may remain in archives where it is not practical or possible to delete it. In addition, we may keep your personal information as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or enforce any of our agreements.
  * **Revocation Of Consent** We rely on the processing of personal information that you have provided. If you revoke your consent for the processing of personal information, then we may no longer be able to provide you services. In some cases, we may limit or deny your request to revoke consent if the law permits or requires us to do so, or if we are unable to adequately verify your identity.
  * **Access To Your Personal Data** If required by law, upon request, we will grant reasonable access to the personal information that we hold about a user. All requests must be directed to the contact in the “Contact Information” section.
  * **Online Tracking** We do not currently recognize browser signals of tracking preferences, which may include “Do Not Track” instructions.

## How We Protect Personal Information

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of any unauthorized access to your personal information we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.

Some of our websites permit you to create an account. When you do you will be prompted to create a password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of your account by someone else that has obtained your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by you. You should notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account.

## How You May Contact Us Regarding Personal Information

If you would like to request access to or the deletion of your personal information, or have any questions, comments, or complaints concerning our privacy practices please contact us at the appropriate address below. We will attempt to respond to all requests or refer you to the appropriate party.

If you are not satisfied with WWT’s response, and are in the European Union, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority

## Miscellaneous

The following additional information relates to our privacy practices:

  * **Transmission of Data to Other Countries** Your personal information may be processed in jurisdictions, like the United States, where privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By submitting your personal information to us you agree to the transfer, storage and processing of your information in such jurisdictions.
  * **Third Party Applications/Websites** We have no control over the privacy practices of websites or applications that we do not own.
  * **Changes to this Privacy Policy** We may change our privacy policy and practices over time. To the extent that our policy changes in a material way, the policy that was in place at the time that you submitted personal information to us will generally govern that information.

**Last Revised: 9 February 2018**
